vroomvroomvroom.com.au 2018-09-03

# Learn About Our Privacy Policy - VroomVroomVroom

Vroom Group Holdings Pty Ltd (ABN 39 162 955 320) and our related companies including Vroom Vroom Vroom Pty Ltd (ACN 050 417 037) and V2B Travel Pte Ltd (UEN 201710991D) (“Vroom”, “we”, “our” or “us”) are committed to the protection of personal privacy within the scope of applicable law. This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personal information that we collect, use and disclose.

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version will be located on our website, and is also available by contacting our Privacy Officer by email or at the address detailed below.

By using our websites, including [vroomvroomvroom.com](https://www.vroomvroomvroom.com/)​, [vroomvroomvroom.com.au](https://www.vroomvroomvroom.com.au/)​, [vroomvroomvroom.com.uk](https://www.vroomvroomvroom.co.uk/index/)​, [vroomvroomvroom.co.nz](https://www.vroomvroomvroom.co.nz/)​, [bargainwheels.com.au](https://www.bargainwheels.com.au/)​, [carhire.com.au](https://www.carhire.com.au/)​, [v2btravel.com](https://v2btravel.com/)​ or any of our apps, or by providing any personal information to us, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as set out in this Privacy Policy. 

## Types of personal information collected

The types of personal information that we collect and hold will vary depending on your dealings with us. This information may include any or all of the following:

  * name, address(es), telephone number(s) and other contact details;
  * electronic address(es); 
  * payment information, including credit card type and expiry date (this information is stored by our third party payment processor); 
  * frequent flyer loyalty reward program number; 
  * driver's licence number;
  * flight number; 
  * other personal information required to provide our services, including age and residency status; and
  * transaction details relating to your use of our products, services or benefits.

We will not collect sensitive information from you or any third party.

From time to time, you may provide us, and we may collect from you, personal information of a third party (for example, for delivery purposes). Where you provide the personal information of a third party, it is your responsibility to ensure that those persons are aware of this Privacy Policy, understand it and agree to accept it.

You do not have to provide us with any personal information, however if you do not do so we may not be able to provide you with the products, services or benefits you have requested.

We also collect the following information from you when you use our website:

  * anonymous non-personal information about how you use our website; and 
  * “cookie” based information that makes your use of our website easier by recording your preferences so that when you return to our website the “cookie” re-loads that information into your web browser. More information set out below.

## How we collect personal information

Generally, we collect personal information directly from you, such as:

  * when you submit information through our websites or one of our apps;
  * when you call us, email, or or use the 'Live Chat' function to speak with one of our customer service agents;
  * in person;
  * in the course of us providing you with a requested product, service or benefit; 
  * when you interact with us via a social media platform; or
  * when you have other dealings with us.

We also collect personal information through:

  * our related bodies corporate;
  * our business partners; and
  * third parties who supply services to us. 

## Why we collect, use and disclose personal information  

We will use the personal information we collect for the purpose disclosed at the time of collection, or otherwise as set out in this Privacy Policy. We will not use your personal information for any other purpose without first seeking your consent, or where authorised or required by law.

We will collect personal information for the following purposes:

  * to establish and maintain your relationship with us;
  * to provide the products or services you have requested from us; or
  * to answer any inquiry you make.

We will disclose personal information as required to the providers of the products and services you have booked or purchased (such as car rental and insurance companies). You accept that not all recipients of your information may have privacy policies or be subject to privacy laws equivalent to us and consent to the disclosure of your personal information for that purpose. 

We may also disclose your personal information to third parties who work with us in our business to provide, promote or improve the products or services you have requested or are interested in, such as:

  * marketing consultants and promotions companies; website hosts; 
  * consultants and professional advisers
  * your company or organisation if you use our services under a corporate account; 
  * one of our program partners if you are a member of their frequent traveller program and you have asked us to send them details of your rental agreement with us; 
  * our contracted service providers (including our payment gateway, market research company and our mail house); 
  * debit and credit card providers; 
  * banks;
  * credit reporting and fraud checking agencies;  
  * debt collection agencies, if you default in payment of monies owed to us; 
  * councils, government and private organisations responsible for the processing or handling of traffic related infringements or the payment of road and traffic tolls;
  * in relation to an accident or claim, insurers, the police and other persons involved in the accident or claim;  
  * driver licensing authorities; and 
  * government, regulatory and law enforcement agencies where the disclosure is required or authorised by law.

## ​Direct marketing

We will also use and disclose your personal information to send direct marketing to you from 

  * us; and
  * our related bodies corporate.

The direct marketing may relate to: 

  * our products and services;
  * the products and services of other parties (such as car rental and insurance companies);
  * new developments we believe may be of interest to you.

​You may opt-out of receiving this direct marketing through the unsubscribe function that will be made available to you with each direct marketing communication.

## How we store and protect personal information

We store personal information in a combination of computer storage facilities, paper-based files and other records. In so doing, we have taken numerous steps to protect your personal information from misuse, interference and loss, and unauthorised access, modification or disclosure.

Additionally, we take reasonable steps to destroy or permanently de-identify personal information when we no longer need it.

The internet is not a secure method of transmitting information. Accordingly, other than where we use secure socket layer technology (SSL) to ensure information is securely transmitted and processed, we cannot and do not accept responsibility for the security of information you send to or receive from us over the internet, or for any unauthorised access or use of that information.

## Do we send personal information overseas?

We are likely to disclose some of your personal information, for the purposes described above, to organisations in New Zealand, United Kingdom, USA, Hong Kong, the Philippines and Ireland.

Some of these countries may not have the same or substantially similar privacy laws as those set out in this privacy policy and the Australian Privacy Principles.  We may not require organisations to which we disclose personal information in those countries to comply with similar privacy laws, and accordingly your personal information may not receive the same protections that it would in Australia.  

By providing your personal information to us, you consent to our disclosure of your personal information to organisations in those countries even though it may not receive the same protections that it would in Australia.  You may request us not to transfer your personal information to the countries listed above, but if you do so we may not be able to provide the services or products you have requested from us.  

## How you can access your personal information

We will take reasonable steps to make sure that the personal information we collect, use or disclose is accurate, complete and up to date. If your personal details change, such as your address or phone number, please contact our Privacy Officer by email or at the address detailed below.

At your request, we will provide you with a copy of any personal information which we hold about you, unless an exception under the Privacy Act 1988 applies. We may charge a fee for retrieving this information, in which case we will inform you of the fee and obtain your agreement to that fee before providing the information.

We will promptly acknowledge and investigate any complaint about the way we manage personal information.

## Cookies

Our website use cookies to undertake targeted advertising across the internet, track user traffic patterns and to better serve you when you revisit a website. A cookie is a small data file that a website may write to your hard drive when you visit it. A cookie file can contain information, such as a user ID which the website uses to track the pages you have visited. You can refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser. However, full functionality for our websites requires the use of cookies.

Information is also generated whenever a page is accessed on our website that records information such as the time, date and specific page. We collect such information for statistical and maintenance purposes that enables us to continually evaluate our website performance.

Our website also collects cookies for use by analytics services, such as Google Analytics. These services use cookies and scripts to collect and store information, including how users interact with our website, errors users encounter when using our website, device identifiers, how often users visit the website, what pages they visit, and what other sites they used prior to coming to the website. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve our website and our services. Please see the following links for more information about Google Analytics:

  * <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>​
  * <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>​
  * <http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html>​ 

We do not tie the information gathered using third party analytics to your personal information.

## Data breaches

We take data breaches seriously and will act in compliance with the Notifiable Data Breaches scheme established by the Privacy Amendment (Notifiable Data Breaches) Act 2017. 

We will use our best endeavours to contain, assess and remedy actual and suspected data breaches as soon as possible and no later than 30 calendar days after the date of the actual or suspected data breach in accordance with our company data breach response policies and procedures.  

Where your personal information held by us is lost or subjected to unauthorised access, modification, use or disclosure or other misuse, and this is this is likely to result in serious harm to you or other individuals, we will take steps to remedy the risk of serious harm as quickly as possible. If we have not been able to prevent the likely risk of serious harm with remedial action, we will notify you, other affected individuals, and the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner. 

## How to contact us or make a complaint

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, if you wish to update information we hold about you or if you wish to make a complaint about our collection, use or disclosure of your personal information under this Privacy Policy, please contact:

The Privacy Officer

Level 1A, 10 Finchley Street, Milton, Queensland, 4064

E-mail: privacy@vroomvroomvroom.com.au

We will take reasonable steps to remedy any issues resulting from our failure to comply with our privacy obligations.

If you are not satisfied with the outcome of your complaint you may refer the matter to the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner (OAIC). 

Telephone: 1300 363 992

enquiries@oaic.gov.au

OAIC complaints page: <http://www.oaic.gov.au/privacy/privacy-complaints>​

_Last updated on 21 August 2018_
